To be, or not to be: that is the question 
Whether His nobler in the mind to suffer 
The slings and arrows of outrageous fortune 
Or to take arms against a sea of troubles 
And by opposing end them? To die: to sleep 
No more; and by a sleep to say we end 
The heart-ache and the thousand natural shocks 
That flesh is heir to, His a consummation 
Devoutly to be wish'd. To die, to sleep 
To sleep: perchance to dream: ay, there's the rub 
For in that sleep of death what dreams may come 
When we have shuffled off this mortal coil 
Must give us pause: there's the respect 
That makes calamity of so long life 